<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bone of cain</title>
    <description>my life stories</description>
    <link>http://boneofcain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://boneofcain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 18:58:36 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 18:58:36 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>how i met the first very bad man.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first man I dated seriously had a totally mundane, normal man name – like Andrew, or Daniel, or Eric. But, I’m going to call him what he was: &lt;em&gt;the first very bad man&lt;/em&gt;, or Vbm1 for short.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was May. I had just turned 18, and I was a few weeks away from graduating high school. The coffee shop I worked at had just gone out of business, and I was desperate for a job. I looked in the local newspaper classifieds and ended up landing a terrible telemarketing gig selling magazines over the phone in some squat, run-down building with moldy carpet and stained ceiling tiles. It was attached to the shittiest gas station in town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first day on the phones, my manager sat me down between two young men. The one on my right, Brett (&lt;em&gt;with two Ts&lt;/em&gt; he always announced when introducing himself), was rail thin, had rotting teeth, and had the longest, knobbiest fingers I’d ever seen. His entire &lt;em&gt;being&lt;/em&gt; smacked of white trash con artist. Not to spoil the story, but I wasn’t wrong about him at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The young man on my left was Vbm1. He was healthier-looking than Brett, and was reclined in his chair, swiveling from side to side. His demeanor was totally effortless and aside from the holey, bleach-stained tshirt he was wearing, he was actually kinda cute. When I sat down, Vbm1 stopped swiveling and straightened up in his chair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was busy trying to connect my headset to the computer when I noticed Vbm1 hunched over his desk out of the corner of my eye. I looked toward him, and saw him scribbling something on a piece of paper.
He looked up, made eye contact with me, and slowly slid the piece of paper toward me. I broke eye contact to look at the paper. It said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;——— sex machine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My eyes followed the scrawled arrow back to Vbm1. He had an almost predatory grin drawn across his face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t remember how I felt in that moment, but I remember what I did. I grabbed my pen and wrote a return note:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;——— &lt;strike&gt;sex&lt;/strike&gt; machine GUN ———&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put the note back on his desk. He followed my arrow back to me. He still had the same stupid fucking grin on his face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s how I met Vbm1. And that’s how what I call the “Longest Lost Year” began.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://boneofcain.com/2016/02/04/first-bad-man/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://boneofcain.com/2016/02/04/first-bad-man/</guid>
        
        <category>vbm1</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>first.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;
I wasn&#39;t actually whittled from the bone of cain. My stepmom used to tell me that I hatched from a rotten egg, fully-grown and surly.
Before that, I assumed that I sprang from a hole in the ground, like the Celts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, I got ahold of a book about biology and learned how human babies are made. I still held onto the idea that I wasn&#39;t human, and was sure the book didn&#39;t apply to my own origin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I eventually found out I was actually born of a human woman. By C-section, and I nearly killed her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This realization was the first disappointment I suffered as a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ccVC5MjZEfs&quot;&gt;Dot King was whittled from the bone of Cain.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://boneofcain.com/2015/09/15/first/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://boneofcain.com/2015/09/15/first/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
